<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="first_question"> When Michael Jordan played for the Chicago Bulls,
            how many NBA Championships did he win? </string>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>
            When Michael Jordan played for the Chicago Bulls,
            how many NBA Championships did he win?
        </item>
        <item>
            Which Williams sister has won more Grand Slam titles?
        </item>
        <item>
            Which racer holds the record for the most Grand Prix wins?
        </item>
        <item>
            Which boxer was known as "The Greatest” and “The People\’s Champion”?
        </item>
        <item>
            What country won the very first FIFA World Cup in 1930?
        </item>
        <item>
            Which hockey team did Wayne Gretzky play for in the \‘80s?
        </item>
        <item>
            How many players should each team have on the field at the
                start of each match?
        </item>
        <item>
            What year was the first iPhone released?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is often seen as the smallest unit of memory?
        </item>
        <item>
            What does "HTTP" stand for?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is twitter\'s original name?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is Samsung\'s country of origin ?
        </item>
        <item>
            What company made the super computer named Watson?
        </item>
        <item>
            What company was founded by Reed Hastings and Marc Randolph?
        </item>
        <item>
            The first cell phone was made in what year?
        </item>
        <item>
            What was the name of the first Apple computer?
        </item>
        <item>
            Who discovered penicillin?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is meteorology the study of?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is the symbol of potassium?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is the hottest planet in the solar system?
        </item>
        <item>
            What planet has the most gravity?
        </item>
        <item>
            What natural disaster uses the Richter scale?
        </item>
        <item>
            What country is the largest coffee producer ?
        </item>
        <item>
            What country invented tea ?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is the name of deer meat?
        </item>
        <item>
            What European country is credited with inventing hot dogs?
        </item>
        <item>
            What human organ has 4 chambers ?
        </item>
        <item>
            How many times does the human heart beat every day?
        </item>
        <item>
            What is the human bodies largest organ ?
        </item>
        <item>
            What bone are babies not born with ?
        </item>
        <item>
            How many taste buds do most human tongues have?
        </item>
        <item>
            What does the acronym AIDS stand for ?
        </item>
        <item>
            What continent is the largest
        </item>
        <item>
            What is the largest desert on earth
        </item>
        <item>
            What is the capital of New Zealand
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>